Bangkok in the 4 Fun Store, Thailand's first address for everything fetish. You
get spandex, latex, fursuits, everything you can imagine and I'll take you with
me today and show you the store. So if you're here make sure to visit.
Forfun is known for their pet suits and they're usually made to measure but I'm
going to try on this tiger suit for you nevertheless.
It's really just super cozy like all the fursuits here and it's also really warm
so I'm glad the store has air conditioning outside it's 33 degrees Celsius and it even has a tail
so fun
this is a molded rubber cap the specialty here is the latex comes from Thailand and it has its
really own good smell.
I love this futuristic design. These kind of molded rubber masks are specialty for fun
and if you ever wanted to be a dragon or dog you should check them out.
It's super thick about 2.5 millimeters and it's awesome.
It's fine, but he's doing great, it's a lot of effort and I think it's going to sit really
snug.
I keep coming back here because the light is just so great and I think it's perfect
to show the corset and it's really a great fit.
I love it! But it's also really tight!
My personal favorite piece is this catsuit because look at the design work and all the applications. It's insane!
I love that they have all different kind of animal masks not only puppies but
reindeer and rabbit and we have a pig here wolf so many to choose from also
the molded latex rubber mask again bunny here dragon so cool this is a massive
choker it's a man-sized but made by Forfun and the price is like 2000 baht
which is around $60 which I think is really really reasonable price for
something like this I love the dark metal here I think it's a really fun
contrast another specialty I found is this rubber cocoon
So it's 3kg and the thickness is 2.5mm, it comes in different sizes and you can also
order it, make your own measurements of course, you can shine it up using the normal latex
China I think it's cool that
with me is mr. s the owner and founder of for fun honey what do you have to be
sorry ha hello thanks for letting me fill in your great story also in the
cafe right now when did you open the store I open this store from 2019
2009 for fun do people have to make an appointment to visit a store or can they
just come yeah thank you everyone who come and no need appointment but if you
need some designer to measurement I recommend to contact us first.
So your specialty is made to measure head suits, tour suits, latex, everything made
to measure?
Yes, that's right.
We have our own workshop and designer.
So you manufacture everything here which is really great.
How many pieces do you have or how many designs?
Right now, on the website, I think it's about 200 or 300.
But more will be up on the website soon.
Around 200 designs.
Wow.
That's the new one.
Right.
Yeah.
Thank you for taking the time.
You're welcome.
I really recommend everyone to just stop here when you're in Bangkok because it's just awesome.
And there's also a cafe, Friday and Saturday open for people from the scene to get together here.
Yes, every Friday is a fetish Friday and Saturday is a dressing day.
And each Saturday we have a different thing.
Okay, great. Thanks for having me today.
Everyone if you're in Bangkok, check out this store. I'll link everything in the description text.
Welcome everyone and thank you so much, Celine, for visiting.
Thanks for you too.
I'm so happy. It's a very wonderful time for me.
Thanks. Alright. Bye everyone.
Bye bye. Thank you.
Sawasdee krab.